<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fannin Family Film Fanatics</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Fannin Family Film Fanatics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a site where we collect movie reviews written by Miles, Leia, Inessa and Brian. We like to watch movies together and we talk about them. Leia got started writing movie reviews online about two years ago (November 2015). Brian wrote his first review in December 2017 and thought it would be fun create a space for the whole family to talk about films. Hope you enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Brian</title>
      <link>/brian/about-brian/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brian/about-brian/</guid>
      <description>Brian is a guy who likes movies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Inessa</title>
      <link>/inessa/about-inessa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/inessa/about-inessa/</guid>
      <description>Inessa likes to cross stitch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Leia</title>
      <link>/leia/about-leia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/leia/about-leia/</guid>
      <description>Leia likes to write and cook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Miles</title>
      <link>/miles/about-miles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/miles/about-miles/</guid>
      <description>Miles likes space and legos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars: The Last Jedi</title>
      <link>/brian/star-wars-the-last-jedi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brian/star-wars-the-last-jedi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Martian</title>
      <link>/leia/2017-12-0-themartian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/leia/2017-12-0-themartian/</guid>
      <description>The movie &amp;ldquo;The Martian&amp;rdquo; ( starring Matt Damon) is a wonderful movie that has earned comments such as &amp;ldquo;Epic&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;The best movie on this or any other planet&amp;rdquo;. Based on a #1 New York Times bestselling novel, this science fiction movie is one of the coolest movies I have ever seen. &amp;ldquo;The Martian&amp;rdquo; is funnily enough rated PG-13 (parental guidence under the age of 13, for those who don&amp;rsquo;t already know).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bread Measurements</title>
      <link>/leia/2016-07-04-breadmeasurements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/leia/2016-07-04-breadmeasurements/</guid>
      <description>I am studying a book on cooking(It&amp;rsquo;s my specialty) .
In it there is a recipy called &amp;ldquo;dutch oven bread&amp;rdquo;;the one that inspiered me.
I am writting this to tell you some intresting(atleast to me) measurments on this dutch oven bread that I will explain to you after the measurments.
The regular measurments, 500 grams flour to 300 grams water.
Aditoin problums,1000 to 600, 2000 to 120,4000 to 240,8000 to 480,16000,to 8160,212000,to 162120.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leias savoury parsols</title>
      <link>/leia/2016-06-15-savoryparcels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/leia/2016-06-15-savoryparcels/</guid>
      <description>I first started learning to bake when I was 7 and a half years old.
Today I am VERY happy to entreduce you to a savory baked good.
So, sit in a comtrable spot, put on your reading glasses and enjoy!
Today I am going to proudly entriduce you to my first working recipy; a savory parsol.
Here are the ingreedients:
1 bag of rough puff pastry(I know,I wrote this only when I was 7)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Despicable Me</title>
      <link>/leia/2016-05-22-despicableme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/leia/2016-05-22-despicableme/</guid>
      <description>Dispicable me is just wow.
It is a good movie because it comes with two others,minions,and I dont know what your name is.
I like this movie because it has a villan who ends up with a kind heart.
My dida thought this movie was hallarious and so do I.
This movie was so great!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>/leia/2016-05-22-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/leia/2016-05-22-home/</guid>
      <description>Like inside out,this movie is about feelings.
And like Zootopia,this movie is:REALLY REALLY AWSOMELY GREAT!!!!!!!!!!!
I like this movie because it is one of those movies that makes you cry and makes your insides soften.
This movie also teaches you a little bit about speaking out and saying somthing someone is doing is wrong and how to stay calm when saying it even if the porson your saying that to is someone that you really really love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zootopia</title>
      <link>/leia/2016-05-22-zootopia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/leia/2016-05-22-zootopia/</guid>
      <description>zootopia is realy great.
I think it is a movie where you learn how some very difrent pepole(and animals) can get along.
My opinion of this movie is that its a very&amp;rsquo;kind hearted&amp;rsquo; movie, meaning most of the charecters are very kind hearted.
My favorite part of this movie was at the very beggening but i&amp;rsquo;m not going to give it away to you because the part is so funny and if I gave it away to you you would have known it already and then the part wouldent have ben funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>starwars</title>
      <link>/leia/2016-05-22-starwars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/leia/2016-05-22-starwars/</guid>
      <description>STARWARS IS THE GREATEST MOVIE I HAVE EVER SEEN!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
All of the movies are just greatly awsome.
My brother has a new bubble wand and he is pretending it is a light-saber.
If I see one of the movies I stare at it in awe like jedi&amp;rsquo;s are swash buckeling pirates.
I wish I was watching starwars right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>/leia/2016-02-28-et/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/leia/2016-02-28-et/</guid>
      <description>Now, this movie is difrent from all my other reveiews. This movie I must say, is worse than all the others. To me this movie is scary. You might ask why. I am going to tell you the most basic two reasons.
1:it&amp;rsquo;s sad 2:It creeps me out. And why would you ever wan&amp;rsquo;t to lose one of your friend&amp;rsquo;s like, forever? Sad right? And changing pink and grey when you&amp;rsquo;re sick, gross.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inside Out</title>
      <link>/leia/2016-02-28-insideout/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/leia/2016-02-28-insideout/</guid>
      <description>so this is inside out. inside out isn&amp;rsquo;t that old. Inside out is all about feelings. And each feeling goes with a color. sadness-I bet you already know-blue. Red is for angry. Green-disgust. Yellow is for joy and puple-fear. I prefer amazing inside out for this movies title. If you just try it you&amp;rsquo;d definitely enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlantis 2</title>
      <link>/leia/2015-11-29-atlantis2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/leia/2015-11-29-atlantis2/</guid>
      <description>Milo and kida are on the lost city of atlantis when milo&amp;rsquo;s old friends sweet,Audry, and others show up.
They say that problum have ben caused on the serfuice.milo agrees to solve them and kida does to.
&amp;ldquo;thare are questoins to be answered,&amp;rdquo;
says kida &amp;ldquo;and the answers to those questoins are not in atlantis&amp;rdquo;
milo kida and thare friends go on three adventures.
in the last one kida gets a spear with the power of atlantis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Brown Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>/leia/2015-11-26-charliebrown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/leia/2015-11-26-charliebrown/</guid>
      <description>Peppermint Patty invites herself and two friends to Charlie Brown&amp;rsquo;s house for Thanksgiving dinner and he won&amp;rsquo;t even be home!
I really liked this movie because the peanut gang movies are sooooo,funny!
Also,this movie includes a bonus epesode featuring the peanut gang sailing to their new land on the mayflower!
Try watching it,its amazing!
Also,snoopy makes a thanksgiving dinner like toast and popcorn and when the children go to charlie brown&amp;rsquo;s grandma&amp;rsquo;s house for thanksgiving dinner,snoopy and woodstock</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elf</title>
      <link>/leia/2015-11-26-elf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/leia/2015-11-26-elf/</guid>
      <description>Baby Buddy accidentally crawls into Santa&amp;rsquo;s bag at an orphanage and goes to Santa&amp;rsquo;s workshop in the North Pole! He grows fast and soon realizes he is not meant to be an elf! He sets out to find his dad and gets swept up in a wonderful adventure!
I saw this movie and I, Leia, think that it&amp;rsquo;s amazing. You should try the movie maybe you can find this movie at a Durham county library called the Southwest Regional Library.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>